where do we begin a year ago these uh cops
and lawyers wouldn't dare cross any of you i mean
what
happened so are you proposing it's simple kill the batman
here's my card bruce this is harvey dent rachel's told
bruce this is harvey dent rachel's told me everything about
you i certainly hope not
you always told me that we'd be together did you
mean it bruce don't make me your only hope for
a normal life
you're alfred right that's sir any you're alfred right that's sir any psychotic
ex-boyfriends i should be psychotic ex-boyfriends i should be aware
of oh you have no idea
good evening ladies and gentlemen
good evening ladies and gentlemen we're tonight's entertainment
well hello
you look nervous
i've seen now would have to become stop men like
him the night is darkest just before the
dawn i promise you the dawn is coming
and here we go
this city deserves a better glass of
criminal i'm gonna give it to him no
we'll see i'll show you
either die a hero
or you live long enough to see yourself become the
will you be wanting the bat puncher in middle of
the day alfred not very subtle the lamborghini
much more
subtle